export const jsQuiz = {
    questions: [
        {
            question:  "I __ a programmer",
            choices: ["are", "am", "is", "be"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "am",
        },
        {
            question:  "She __ two children.",
            choices: ["have", "has", "have got", "having"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "has",
        },
        {
            question:  "He __ like playing soccer.",
            choices: ["doesn't", "don't", "is not to", "do not"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "doesn't",
        },
        {
            question:  "Iâ€™m watching an interesting movie right now. What __ doing?",
            choices: ["is you", "you is", "you are", "are you"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "are you",
        },
        {
            question:  " __ he go for a walk in the evening?",
            choices: ["do", "does", "is", "was"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Does",
        },
        {
            question:  "She liked the party, __?",
            choices: ["doesn't she", "did she", "didn't she", "does she"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "didn't she",
        },
        {
            question:  "You __ your homework before you came to the lesson!",
            choices: ["should do", "should be done", "should have done", "should be doing"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "should have done",
        },
        {
            question:  "He suffers __ her absence more than he'd like us to think.",
            choices: ["on", "from", "of", "at"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "from",
        },
        {
            question:  "She is thinking __ to the United States in three weeks.",
            choices: ["to go", "going", "about going", "of going"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "of going",
        },
        {
            question:  "I wish I __ that.",
            choices: ["hadn't done", "not to do", "am not doing", "don't do"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "hadn't done",
        },
        {
            question: "I __ all my work by tomorrow.",
            choices: ["am going to do", "will do", "will be doing", "will have done"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "will have done",
        },
        {
            question:  "Do you mind __ the window?",
            choices: ["open", "opened", "to open", "opening"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "opening",
        },
        {
            question:  "In spite of __ poor he traveled a lot",
            choices: ["he was", "being", "him", "he's"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "being",
        },
        {
            question:  "He is looking forward __ his friends again.",
            choices: ["to see", "see", "to seeing", "seeing"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "to seeing",
        },
        {
            question:  "If you __ to his place tomorrow, he will help you with your homework.",
            choices: ["will come", "comes", "come", "to come"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "come",
        },
        {
            question:  "If I __ you, I would do it immediately.",
            choices: ["were", "am", "to be", "have got"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "were",
        },
        {
            question:  "If he had studied well, he ___________ his exams last year",
            choices: ["would pass", "would have been passing", "would have been passed", "would have passed"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "would have passed",
        },
        {
            question:  "I ________ play American football some years ago, but I don't play it anymore",
            choices: ["did use to", "was use to", "used to", "use to"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "used to",
        },
        {
            question:  "She ____________ here for three years already.",
            choices: ["works", "is working", "has working", "has been working"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "has been working",
        },
        {
            question:  "When I came home yesterday my wife _____ already.",
            choices: ["has gone", "has been gone", "had gone", "had been gone"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "had gone",
        },
        {
            question:  "She came to my place when I _______ a book",
            choices: ["was reading", "read", "had been read", "reads"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "was reading",
        },
        {
            question:  " I have been sitting at home ________.",
            choices: ["by myself", "on myself", "in my own", "from myself"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "by myself",
        },
        {
            question:  " She made me _____ that she was a doctor.",
            choices: ["thinking", "to think", "think", "thought"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "think",
        },
        {
            question:  "When I came home, dinner _______ already.",
            choices: ["was being cooked", "cooked", "was cooking", "had been cooked"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "had been cooked",
        },
        {
            question:  "My neighbor doesn't like cooking and_______.",
            choices: ["neither do I", "neither does I", "so do I", "so does I"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "neither do I",
        }
        
    ]
}

export const resultInitialState = {
    score: 0,
    correctAnswers: 0, 
    wrongAnswers: 0,
}

